Guide to the 1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Records 1974-2012
1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Records
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Records, 1974-2012
6347
1199SEIU Rochester; SEIU 1199 Upstate; 1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East; Service Employees International Union (SEIU); SEIU Local 1199 (New York, N.Y.)
3.2 linear ft.
Records.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
27.72 cubic feet
SUBJECTS
Names:
Service Employees International Union.; Service Employees International Union. Local 1199 (New York, N.Y.); Service Employees International Union. Local 1199 (Rochester, N.Y.)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
6347 PUBS: 1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Publications
CONTAINER LIST
- Pension Fund Trustees Meetings, 2004-2008 (Box 1)
  - Resolution of the Board of Trustees, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    June 11, 2004
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees: Training and Upgrading Fund, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    December 2, 2004
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    April 11, 2005
  - Annual Meeting of the National Benefit Fund and Employee Pension Fund, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    June 23, 2006; 1 of 3
  - Annual Meeting of the National Benefit Fund and Employee Pension Fund, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    June 23, 2006; 2 of 3
  - Annual Meeting of the National Benefit Fund and Employee Pension Fund, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    June 23, 2006; 3 of 3
  - Benefit and Pension Fund Joint Session, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    June 2006
  - Joint Session of the National Benefit and Pension Funds, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    December 14, 2006; 1 of 3
  - Joint Session of the National Benefit and Pension Funds, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    December 14, 2006; 2 of 3
  - Joint Session of the National Benefit and Pension Funds, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    December 14, 2006; 3 of 3
  - Meeting of the Boards of Trustees, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    December 15, 2006; 1 of 2
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    December 15, 2006; 2 of 2
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    March 21, 2007; 1 of 3
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    March 21, 2006; 2 of 3
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    March 21, 2007; 3 of 3
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    December 13, 2007
  - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    July 16, 2008; 1 of 3
  - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    July 16, 2008; 2 of 3
  - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    July 16, 2008; 3 of 3
  - Joint Session of the Board of Trustees, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    July 17, 2008
  - Joint Session of the Board of Trustees, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    July 18, 2008
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    December 11, 2008
  - Joint Budget Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    December 11, 2008; 1 of 2
  - Joint Budget Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    December 11, 2008; 2 of 2
- Pension Fund Trustees Meetings, 2009-2011; Other Records (Box 2)
  - Executive Director's Annual Joint Report, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    2009 through First Quarter 2010
  - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    July 21, 2010; Section 1, 1-8; 1 of 3
  - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    July 21, 2010; Section 2, 1-10; 2 of 3
  - Joint Session of the Board of Trustees, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    July 21, 2010; 3 of 3
  - Joint Budget Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    12/16/10
  - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    7/14/11; 1 of 2
  - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    7/14/2011; 2 of 2
  - Pension Plan and Memorandum, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Service Employees Pension Fund of Upstate NY, 1992-2006 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Health Care Employees Pension Fund: Agreement and Declaration of Trust, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Union Trustee Training, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    June 1, 2006
  - 1993 Legislative Conference and Legislative Action Packet 103rd Congress (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1993 Legislative Conference: Issue Briefing Materials (Box 2, Folder 13)
    May 24, 1993
  - Communities at Work Toolbox, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    1 of 2
  - Communities at Work Toolbox, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    2 of 2
  - Dues Payment Summary Sheet- Rochester, NUHHCE/SEIU, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Sections 1-4; 1 of 2
  - Dues Payment Summary Sheet- Rochester, NUHHCE/SEIU, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Sections 5-10; 2 of 2
  - 1998 Rolex Awards for Enterprise Application (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Biographies, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Marilyn Gaines, George Gresham
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1974-2012 (Box 3)
  - Agreement with Bertrand Chaffee Hospital and Jennie B. Richmond Home, 2006-2009 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    9/13/06- 9/12/09
  - Agreements with Blossom Health Care Center, 2006-2008 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    5/1/06-4/30/08
  - Agreement with Brooks Memorial Hospital, 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    5/1/05-4/30/08
  - Agreement with Brylin Hospitals, 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    6/30/05-7/1/08
  - Agreements with Continuing Developmental Services, Inc., 1988-1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    3/12/88-3/31/90 and 4/9/94- 4/12/96
  - Agreement with Corning Hospital, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    11/30/00-6/30/03
  - Agreement with DePaul Adult Care Communities, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    7/1/94-12/31/96
  - Agreements with GMR Living Centers, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Agreements with Greater New York Health Care Facilities, 2002-2008 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    10/1/02-4/30/05 and 6/1/04- 4/30/08
  - Agreements with Jennifer Matthews Nursing and Rehabilitation Center, 2002-2008 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Agreements with Kaleida Health, 2000-2005 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    12/1/00-5/31/05; 1 of 2
  - Agreement with Kaleida Health, 2008-2011 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    6/1/08-5/31/11; 2 of 2
  - Agreements with League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes of New York, 1974-2008 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    1974-1976, 11/1/01-4/30/05, 6/1/04-4/30/08
  - Agreement with Lockport Memorial Hospital, 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    9/18/05-3/31/08
  - Agreement with Mount St. Mary's Hospital, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    8/18/06
  - Agreement with Niagara Falls Memorial Medical Center, 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    4/21/05-4/21/08
  - Agreement with Sheehan Memorial Hospital, 2006-2008 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    1/1/06-4/30/08
  - Agreement with Sodexho at Sisters of Charity Hospital, 2007-2010 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    7/16/07-7/16/10
  - Agreements with Strong Memorial Hospital, 2002-2007 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Agreements with Strong Memorial Hospital, 2000-2012 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Agreements with VNA Home Care Services, 2006-2008 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    12/1/06-5/31/08
  - Agreements with Wesley Gardens Nursing Home, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. at Local 1199, New York City, 1968 (Box 4)
- Gerry Hudson MLAC Speech, March 2011 (Box 5)